[{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980314049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17659,"timeElapsed":92096},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8342,"timeElapsed":100441},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13043,"timeElapsed":113486},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5686,"timeElapsed":119175},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5855,"timeElapsed":125033},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6105,"timeElapsed":131140},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980357353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4258,"timeElapsed":135400},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":17576,"timeElapsed":152978},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"17","question":"What is your most treasured memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5888,"timeElapsed":158867},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":19335,"timeElapsed":181081},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4140,"timeElapsed":185223},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":19429,"timeElapsed":204653},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":6760,"timeElapsed":211415},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":11629,"timeElapsed":223045},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":225698},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2842,"timeElapsed":228542},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10435,"timeElapsed":238978},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":10110,"timeElapsed":249090},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":17003,"timeElapsed":267505},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3051,"timeElapsed":270557},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3365,"timeElapsed":273923},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2976,"timeElapsed":276901},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4100,"timeElapsed":281003},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3067,"timeElapsed":284071},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4244,"timeElapsed":288317},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7048,"timeElapsed":295368},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4517,"timeElapsed":299886},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530985,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9143,"timeElapsed":309032},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16129,"timeElapsed":326556},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2987,"timeElapsed":329545},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2906,"timeElapsed":332453},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2712,"timeElapsed":335167},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2706,"timeElapsed":337875},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":340463},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4852,"timeElapsed":345317},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6723,"timeElapsed":352041},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2520,"timeElapsed":354563},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10891,"timeElapsed":366570},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4510,"timeElapsed":371082},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":374597},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3277,"timeElapsed":377876},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980602471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":380518},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3075,"timeElapsed":383595},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8842,"timeElapsed":392438},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":19030,"timeElapsed":411469},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3786,"timeElapsed":415257},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641312,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4101,"timeElapsed":419359},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9969,"timeElapsed":430547},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2298,"timeElapsed":432847},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":435843},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2553,"timeElapsed":438398},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5303,"timeElapsed":443702},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2632,"timeElapsed":446336},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2690,"timeElapsed":449027},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":8931,"timeElapsed":457960},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5903,"timeElapsed":463865},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7540,"timeElapsed":472488},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3586,"timeElapsed":476077},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2466,"timeElapsed":478545},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3956,"timeElapsed":482503},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5006,"timeElapsed":487510},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2377,"timeElapsed":489889},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2635,"timeElapsed":492525},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":10069,"timeElapsed":502596},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5491,"timeElapsed":508089},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":12253,"timeElapsed":521490},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5975,"timeElapsed":527466},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3035,"timeElapsed":530502},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4245,"timeElapsed":534748},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":5212,"timeElapsed":539962},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3099,"timeElapsed":543063},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2738,"timeElapsed":545803},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3811,"timeElapsed":549616},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2945,"timeElapsed":552563},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":40359,"timeElapsed":595368},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3477,"timeElapsed":598846},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3043,"timeElapsed":601891},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4299,"timeElapsed":606191},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4060,"timeElapsed":610252},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4309,"timeElapsed":614563},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3826,"timeElapsed":618391},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4350,"timeElapsed":622743},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2864,"timeElapsed":625609},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13635,"timeElapsed":641481},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2112,"timeElapsed":643595},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6889,"timeElapsed":650486},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":653866},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":657766},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980887273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":7553,"timeElapsed":665320},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4694,"timeElapsed":670016},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5663,"timeElapsed":675681},{"subjectID":"15r9qzrw0l","prolificID":"607c9f94cc974d4ea1dc22c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2687bfaebfc6fda7512","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4244,"timeElapsed":679927}]